Victims of the virtual currency
Fullcoin scam
are still pursuing their claim.
Rumor has it, even Yip Wing-kei,
the Showbiz King has fallen victim
to the scam.
Businessman Wong Sai-lung who
launched Fullcoin
is allegedly the mastermind behind the scam.
Just drinking water?
I want to clear my mind before the job.
The Boss said the target is a handful.
You should eat while you can.
Cheung Tin-fai, Fullcoin victim #1,
triad thug.
First rate muscleman, but lousy with
personal finance.
Fallen prey to the scam, heavily in debt.
After his wife and child left him,
he reluctantly became a hitman.
Brother Fu, have an egg tart.
Chin Tai-fu, mastermind of the
Fullcoin scam.
A heartless billionaire.
Allegedly he conned a fortune from
Yip Wing-kei
who put a price on his head.
He's now on the run.
Did you see the news today?
Well...
Don't "well" me!
Don't speak English!
Pretending to be a foreigner?
You're just a punk.
Why didn't your man get to work?
You know the Showbiz King hired a hit on me.
You want me to die first?
The Showbiz King doesn't go out
and is surrounded by bodyguards.
The cost to kill him is very high.
You only gave me a $2M budget.
It's not that easy to find a hitman.
Don't talk to me about money.
You've been on my payroll long enough.
Don't worry. I hired a hitman.
I'm waiting for the right moment
to give the order.
The Showbiz King will be a dead man.
Wong Sai-lung, triad boss.
He started out doing the dirty work
for Chin Tai-fu.
New to the business world,
he's in charge of Fullcoin.
He and Chin Tai-fu created
the Fullcoin scam.
Hired a hitman to take out his boss' enemy.
The location is set. Get ready.
Do it today.
Get ready!
We'll tell you who the target is later.
Why so secretive?
Your wife and two daughters
have boarded the plane safely.
I'm putting you up in a hotel.
Which one?
I picked a boutique hotel.
Less traffic, more manageable.
I instructed the hotel
no one should know you're in the hotel.
The Showbiz King won't find you.
Roy, drive!
Where to, Boss?
Which hotel?
Hotel de Maze.
Wong Sai-lung, person in charge of Fullcoin.
He and Chin Tai-fu created
the Fullcoin scam.
Hired a hitman to take out his boss.
Target location...
Hotel de Maze.
What about the weapon?
It's ready. It's inside the hotel.
Ask for Sister Fong when you arrive.
Here's another gem.
The hell with it, for the money,
I don't care anymore.
Law Siu-fong, Fullcoin victim #2,
greedy chambermaid and doting mother.
Willing to do anything for a quick buck
to pay off her son's debt.
(Brother Kui)
(Pick-up code)
(Correct Pick-up code)
(Please pay the fee)
What? I had to pay?
Brother Fu, the room is booked in my name.
I'll check in for you.
You expect me to walk in like this?
I know you prefer the back door.
I got you a staff card.
Take the staff elevator up.
No one will know, OK?
Make sure you check the room carefully.
Of course, don't worry!
You bossed me around long enough.
You don't trust me and you're cheap.
You think $2M can take out Yip Wing-kei?
$2M is enough to kill you.
Mr. Wong, you're letting Mr. Chin
go up by himself?
He's suspicious and prefers to check
everything himself.
What can I do?
Thank you.
Honey, I saw online the jacuzzi in
the Ambassador Suite is beautiful.
It's worth the money.
Chin Chi-tat, today is the deadline.
Pay me before 12 o'clock.
Chin Chi-tat, Fullcoin victim #3.
A slave to designer labels,
a middle-class big spender who
spends beyond his means.
He dotes on his wife.
I'm sorry, Mr. and Mrs. Chin.
The sprinkler system is not working
in the Ambassador Suite.
It's temporarily closed.
What? Just when we're about to check in?
We can put you in the Executive Suite.
It's OK, Honey.
The Executive Suite should be nice.
Who says it's OK?
I told all my besties
we booked the Ambassador Suite
for our wedding anniversary.
What can I tell them now?
Chan Lai-sa, materialistic wife
and social media addict.
You have a full head of white hair!
Are you Sister Fong?
Of course!
Three outfits?
You need them for filming, right?
It's better to have spares.
I don't want you to keep coming back to me.
$2,000 for three sets.
$2,000?
Look at the bleach stain! That's too much!
Without the stain, how can I write them off?
I won't be able to give them to you, pal.
Fork over the money, $2,000!
Target...
Hey, you can't go that way.
That's for staff only.
Go to the back, hurry!
Mr. Wong, your Ambassador Suite is ready.
Thank you.
I thought they said it was closed.
I checked online, only the Ambassador Suite
has a gold keycard.
Brother Fu, I'm going up with
the bodyguards.
It's the second one on the 12/F after
you get off the elevator.
Is that the guy in charge of Fullcoin,
who ripped off a lot of people?
What's his name?
Wong Sai-lung.
You wanted to invest in it too.
Luckily, I stopped you.
Or else, you would have been cleaned out.
Yes, good thing I listened to you.
Why would anyone need so many bodyguards?
It's best not to mess with a triad boss.
Mr. and Mrs. Chin, have you decided?
We'll take the Executive Suite.
It's OK, Honey!
The difference in money
should buy us a nice candlelit dinner
for your pictures.
Sister Fong, you're in luck.
They put you on the 12/F.
The guests of the Ambassador Suite
are usually big tippers.
They updated the guest list.
Who is it?
Check your staff app.
A couple checked into the
Executive Suite on the 12/F.
They're celebrating their
wedding anniversary.
They should be big tippers too.
You're in luck.
Sister Fong, here's another gem.
(Ambassador Suite and Executive Suite)
Where is it?
The second one?
This should be it.
Welcome to our hotel, Mr. Chin.
You know me?
Of course!
While your wife is not around,
surprise her with these flowers.
My wife is here?
Chin Tai-fu took the Ambassador Suite.
But Wong Sai-lung checked in just now.
That's the job of a minion.
You and Mrs. Chin checked into
our Executive Suite.
I'm not mistaken.
I think you mean us.
This Mr. Chin is in the Ambassador Suite.
This clown's last name is also Chin?
Why is he being so helpful?
He's looking for perks because
he recognizes me?
Mr. Chin...
Yes!
I have worked with your group before.
I wonder if you remember me.
He's looking for a business deal.
Thanks for your help.
Let's talk when we have a chance.
Why not now?
I can take pictures of your
Ambassador Suite.
No...please get some rest, Mr. Chin.
We're right next door.
Please call me on the house phone.
What's wrong?
You can't rush into a deal.
He's next door. We'll get our chance.
Brother Fu...
Are you satisfied with the room?
I know you don't like the hotel linen.
I brought your personal bedding over.
I'll get that changed for you later.
Am I here on vacation?
I'm being hunted down.
You booked me into the most flamboyant
room in the hotel.
Are you stupid or what?
You don't understand, Brother Fu.
This floor has the least traffic.
It's the safest.
Least traffic?
Yes.
Just now, right outside,
I saw a couple check in.
You said it was the second room
after I got out of the elevator.
Even the chambermaid recognized me.
I'm sorry, Brother Fu.
I didn't know you took the staff elevator.
I'll file a complaint right away.
You do that as you want.
Don't use my name.
Tell them to turn off the CCTV
on this floor.
Turn it off?
I passed by the security room.
Those clowns were shooting the breeze.
If the hitman disguised as a
security guard and saw the CCTV,
he'll know where I am.
How can you protect me?
But if we turned off the CCTV,
if the hitman showed up,
no one would know. That's too dangerous.
If it's not dangerous, why would I need
people around me?
Who's calling the shots now? Me or you?
You, of course! Everyone follows your lead.
Does that hurt?
Don't worry!
I hired these two from the #1
security consultant in the world.
They're the best of the best.
No English!
They're the top.
You picked this consultant yourself.
It must be safe and reliable.
Get out...
I'll leave you now. I'm right downstairs.
Call me if you need me.
OK, I'm going. Bye!
(Timer)
Disguise, check.
Escape route, check.
Weapon, check.
(Honey)
Honey?
Don't call me that anymore. We're divorced.
Did you put money in my account?
Yes! $250K.
Shit!
Don't curse me!
No...I'm not. I'll call you right back.
Target in Ambassador Suite on the 12/F.
Get inside to change the bedding.
Hurry up.
There are five bullets left.
I only need one.
What's wrong with you?
You screwed up the guest's name?
No, I addressed him as Mr. Chin.
He answered me
and asked me if I recognized him.
Don't bother to deny it.
A greeting is most important
in the hotel business.
You screwed up his name
and affected the most important
guest in the hotel.
You are fired.
I know you never liked me.
This is your excuse to settle
a personal score.
I'll tell management you set me up.
Don't think you can fool me.
You have stolen from the hotel.
Clothes, wine and sold them for profit.
I checked the linen room.
Three uniforms are missing.
You must have sold them.
My son is in the hospital.
He needs money for his surgery.
That's because he's stupid enough
to buy Fullcoin and got himself in debt
and then tried to kill himself.
That's enough, Yu Lo!
If you didn't look the other way,
I wouldn't have the chance to
steal anything.
Besides, I cut you in on the money I made.
I kept a record.
We're a team, before your shift is over,
if you bring back the three uniforms,
I'll pretend nothing happened.
Or else, you are fired.
I will call the Police and charge you
for theft.
Get out!
Fine. I'll get them back.
It's not here...
Sister Fong, I forgot the ice bucket.
Didn't he need the uniform for filming?
What is he doing with the housekeeping cart?
Who cares? I need the uniforms back.
Hey, Silver Fox!
Why are you posing as hotel staff?
What?
I don't care what you're up to.
I'll give you back your $2,000.
I want all three uniforms back.
I don't know what you mean. Out of my way.
Hey...
Hello, I'm coming.
Hey, come back...
A gun?
Is Silver Fox a hitman after Mr. Chin?
If he's caught by the Police,
and they found out I sold him the uniform,
will I be an accomplice?
It's murder. Should I call the Police?
I have you to thank if I got fired.
You lost your way and complained about me!
You can go to Hell.
Law Siu-fong, what are you doing here?
Get to work!
I told you to look for the uniforms,
that doesn't mean you don't have to work.
Are you done here?
Go to the 10/F, someone just checked out.
I don't have time to do both.
Just return the uniforms before
your shift is over.
Or else, don't blame me.
Watch it!
Fine, I'll look.
Calling the Police is a big deal.
Better let sleeping dogs lie.
A4 Hidagyu for two.
Thank you.
I can finally check in.
Please sign here, Sir!
Something wrong with the bill?
No. It's OK.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
Cheers, Honey...
Let me get this...
Hello?
Chin Chi-tat, you have stalled me
for six months...
You must pay me today.
I really don't have the money.
I invested my company in Fullcoin.
I lost all my cash flow.
If you don't pay me today,
I'll show up at your office and your house.
Don't...I can't tell my wife.
Hello?
Honey, what's wrong with you lately?
You seem tight on money.
When you signed the bill and
tipped room service,
you looked like you had toothache.
No...I do have toothache.
Are you OK?
Probably from staying up late.
We're on staycation. Forget work.
Why did you kiss up to that guy just now?
You need insight when you do business.
Remember back then,
I was the first person to think of
the shared wardrobe concept.
That's how we make money.
You're a biz wiz, but I'm not.
That's why I must work hard.
True. Only because of you,
this biz wiz sold her business.
You really must be good to me.
Your husband is a grateful man.
Honey, this is for you.
That's better.
Well? Do you like it?
This bag...
was the most rented item
back then in the shared wardrobe days.
That was three years ago.
It's our third wedding anniversary.
I bought it because I think it's meaningful.
Happy third anniversary.
I didn't go for anything meaningful.
Here...
Thanks, Honey!
This is not yet available on the market!
Only VIPs can pre-order.
It'll be launched in three months.
It looks expensive.
Stop talking about money.
Money should be made, not saved.
You need to meet with clients,
you must look presentable.
The food is not really that great.
Let's go to the south of France this year.
I'll be very busy this year,
I may not get much time off.
You're always busy,
but I don't see any actual results.
Answer it. Work is more important...
Hello?
I have done all I can for you.
Before midnight tonight, just pay me
the interest.
You need to give me time, pal.
I'll need time to sell stuff.
Did you hear what I said?
What are you selling me?
Hey, are you changing the sheets?
What's taking so long?
Yes!
Get over here!
Let me check...
Shit!
What's wrong?
Just checking to see if I forgot anything.
Hello, Mr. Chin.
Changing the sheets? Go ahead.
Sure.
Without the gun,
I can't fight three of them.
This is my only chance to get him up close.
I may not get another chance.
It's not worth taking my chances.
Clear the table for me first.
Yes, Mr. Chin.
Why is he staring at me?
Did he figure out who I am?
Turn down the air-con a bit.
No, don't cower.
Sure.
Use the pad.
Are you here to kill me?
Mr. Chin...you got this all wrong...
I saw you sneaking around this morning.
See? You have my picture.
Actually...I'm a huge fan.
I only wanted your autograph.
A fan? Then you should know me well.
What type of movie stars do I like?
Yu Ssu-ting!
Ting my foot!
Everyone knows I like middle-aged chicks.
Tell me or I'll break your arm.
I'm sorry, Mr. Chin.
I was forced to take this job.
Please let me go.
Did Yip Wing-kei order the hit?
The billionaire Yip Wing-kei is my Boss?
Quit your act!
Is everything OK, Mr. Chin?
I'm OK.
My Boss is Chit Chat Kui.
I don't know who he works for.
Chit Chat Kui? He works for Sai-lung.
I heard screaming.
Was the housekeeper up to no good?
He held Mr. Chin hostage and forced him
to say OK?
Easy...Mr. Chin!
Sorry to interrupt.
Who said you could come in? Get out!
Of course, Mr. Chin!
Sai-lung that ingrate!
He used my money to kill me!
I'll pay you double to kill him.
What? You're my Boss' Boss?
I'm your Boss' Boss' Boss.
Kill him for me.
Wong Sai-lung? The weasel behind Fullcoin?
He was the creep who landed me in debt.
My Boss works for him?
Punks are not to be trusted.
That weasel Sai-lung spread the rumor
about Yip Wing-kei putting a price
on my head
so I would give him money
to hire a hitman to kill him.
But he used my money to hire
a stooge like you to kill me instead.
Don't you think he deserves to die?
A hired gun hired another gun.
He asked for it.
I'll take double and kill him for you.
That's $4M.
The job was $2M?
I only got $500K!
You took $500K.
I'll double that and pay you $1M.
$1M is better than $500K.
I have long wanted to kill Wong Sai-lung.
You're on.
What?
I'll kill Wong Sai-lung.
Wait! Take off your clothes.
I can't believe at a juncture like this,
Mr. Chin is in the mood for that.
Who can resist a stud cupcake?
Here!
He took his clothes off.
Mr. Chin must be a cross-dresser.
Where's the cart?
No clothes, no gun, how can I kill anyone?
Why does Sai-lung want me dead?
Because I made him the fall guy
in the Fullcoin scam?
Luckily, the bodyguards were hired
from the agent I picked.
They probably don't work for him.
But why did they let the hitman through?
Did Sai-lung pay them off too?
What are you looking at?
Close the door!
Yes, Mr. Chin.
Looks like it.
Sai-lung probably used them to
keep an eye on me
and report back to him.
If I stayed, I'm as good as dead.
Didn't you say earlier your husband
seems stingy towards you
and didn't spend as much time with you?
How's your anniversary?
At least he brought me to the
Ambassador Suite of this hotel.
That's good.
Don't forget to make a video and show me.
I heard their jacuzzi is very pretty.
Show me the video, hurry!
Yes, it's quite nice.
But my husband is using it right now.
Honey, my business partner is nearby.
I need to go talk to him.
I can't talk now. I have something to do.
Be careful!
Of what?
Why does he have to take a bath
to see his partner?
Didn't you say he's been acting weird?
Maybe there's another woman.
We just had a small argument.
I think he's stepping out for
some fresh air.
What if he's stepping out to see
another woman?
You better follow him.
OK, I'll go check on him.
Gotta go. Bye!
Hello, Roy?
You have reached the voice mail of 98...
Voice mail?
Hello?
Hello, Mrs. Chin?
It's Chin Tai-fu from next door.
I know, you sent me to the 10/F
so I won't have time to find the uniforms
and then you can fire me.
You evil witch, I wish you won't
live to see tomorrow...
What is that?
People nowadays have no shame.
This is outrageous!
People on the 10/F don't do refills?
Hello? It's a real gun. You want it?
Try it out first, if it's a fake,
you're paying me double the interest.
This isn't thick enough.
Excuse me, I'm here to see Mr. Chin.
What about?
That's none of your business.
Open the door!
Before you go in, mind if I frisk you?
Brother Fu...
Mind if frisk you?
What game are you playing?
Sorry, Mr. Chin!
Sorry...it's boring in the room.
Let's go get something to eat.
Sure!
I'll go down to take a break.
Wait for me up here.
Mr. Chin, it's dangerous for you
to run around.
It's quite nice inside the suite.
Why don't you call room service?
You can relax inside while you eat.
How?
I'd like you to show me.
How dangerous is it to go downstairs
for a bite?
Just wait here.
Mr. Chin is quite unbridled.
He doesn't care her husband is next door.
He takes both man and woman.
Shall we still follow him?
Of course! If anything happens to him,
we're in deep trouble.
Mr. Chin...
I told you not to follow me.
Wait in my room.
Why is the door locked?
Rats! My key card is inside.
Anyone in there?
When your luck is against you...
I'll need to get the spare key.
What a waste of time!
Thank you.
I need your help with something.
Help? How can I help you?
My bodyguards are a pain.
I need your help to ditch them.
Mr. Chin, you promised me
I can take pictures of the Ambassador Suite.
Sure. I'll give you the key card later.
Great!
All these towels should be enough.
The bullet won't get through.
Hello?
Boss?
Where the hell are you?
I'm downstairs at the hotel.
Bring the car around.
I can't. I thought you'd be safe
at the hotel.
I went to Shenzhen to find out
who accepted the hit on you.
Shenzhen? What did you find out?
A hitman syndicate took the order
and they sent several hitmen after you.
It's dangerous out there.
What?
I'm on my way back.
Stay in the hotel.
It's safer with two bodyguards around you.
Why did Roy go north at this juncture?
Did Sai-lung bribe him?
He said he was meeting his business partner.
Sorry, something came up. I can't help you.
What is it?
Hi, I was the last guest in this room.
I think I left something behind.
Can I come in and take a look?
Go talk to the reception.
Roy worked for me for years.
Would he betray me?
If he was telling the truth,
there are several hitmen after me.
Would I live to leave this hotel?
What are you doing here?
We're worried about you.
We figure you may need the car.
So we split up
and check the lobby and the car park.
He can't be that smart.
Roy must have tipped him off.
I can't beat them both.
I shouldn't take them head on.
I need to find a way to ditch them.
Mr. Chin, if you have relaxed,
let's go back upstairs.
OK!
Thanks, Mr. Chin.
Chin Chi-tat, open the door!
Are you in there? I know you're inside!
Chin Chi-tat, I recognize your ringtone.
How dare you hang up on me!
Open the door!
My uniform!
Aren't you Mrs. Chin from the
12/F Executive Suite?
You're not a staff member,
why are you wearing our uniform?
I'm so glad to see you.
My husband is cheating on me
inside this room.
Can you open the door for me?
How about this?
OK...tell me,
where did you get this uniform?
In the backstairs by the elevator,
inside the laundry cart.
It was inside a bag.
The laundry cart? Was there another uniform?
Yes...hurry up!
Chin Chi-tat...
There's no one here.
I'm sure I heard his ringtone.
Did I make a mistake?
Maybe you heard wrong
because you were too nervous?
Maybe your husband is waiting for you
in your suite.
Why don't you give me the uniform
and go back upstairs to look
for your husband?
Look at this!
That only proves the last guest was a woman.
It's perfectly normal.
Just give me back the uniform.
A used condom!
It's normal for a woman to have a boyfriend.
Give me the uniform.
Hey!
There's another room?
Hey...
Chin Chi-tat...your creep!
What are you doing there crouching down?
Where's the other woman?
What woman? There's no one here.
It's not what you think.
What have you done?
I just came into this room.
Whatever happened in here
had nothing to do with me.
If you were never in the room,
how did you know what was inside?
I'll explain later. I'm in a hurry...
Chin Chi-tat, where are you going?
You better explain this...
Hey you... don't go yet...
Are you cheating on me?
Give me back the uniform!
One down...
Another one in the laundry cart
in the backstairs.
Then I'll find Silver Fox and get
the one he's wearing.
Where's the laundry cart?
Do I have to look floor to floor?
Wait, how stupid of me!
Let me see...at this hour,
they're collecting the laundry.
All the laundry carts will be in the
laundry room on the ground floor.
Yes!
Don't scratch the gun! Go away!
He's no fun. Let's go.
Is it a real gun?
We have a deal.
That's your interest for this month.
Manager...
Thanks for your hospitality.
Dinner was delicious.
You're helping us with our Feng Shui,
showing our hospitality is the least
we can do.
The manager seems to believe
everything this woman said.
You think she's any good?
That's Sylvia the psychic!
She's a big hit because she's
pretty and gifted.
I'd like to have her tell my fortune.
Sylvia...
I'm such a big fan...
You're so pretty...
I watched your livecast last night...
Can I take a picture with you?
Thank you.
I want one too...
Hey!
Manager!
Why do you seem so flustered?
I'm looking for something.
What?
Excuse me...lately, have you been
losing things you want?
and things you don't want keep
pestering you?
Yes!
Let me help you with divination.
Pen Fairy...
This lady wants to know her future...
Look, it's moving...
I told you the Pen Fairy is real...
Thank you, Pen Fairy!
What does this mean?
The Chinese character "one"
and the number 18?
You'll know when the time comes.
Where's the laundry cart from the 10/F?
I had to go floor to floor again?
While I'm away,
whatever I want to happen
should have happened.
The key is I have an alibi.
If anything happens to that
creep Chin Tai-fu,
the cops won't connect that to me.
Using his own money to kill him
was a perfect plan.
Brother Lung!
Well? Did the hitman show up?
No.
No?
Did anything unusual happen?
Yes!
What?
He's into both man and woman.
Get serious.
Listen up, nothing happened now
doesn't mean nothing will.
Stay on your toes.
Right, Brother Lung.
Who did Chit Chat Kui hire?
What took him so long?
What's the matter with you?
Why didn't the hitman take action?
He didn't?
He took the money but did nothing.
What now?
I never let you down all these years, right?
It's just a matter of time, don't worry.
I got something for you.
This is the gun I gave the hitman.
You're kidding!
No! Now I know why the hitman did nothing.
He lost the gun!
Who did you hire for the job?
He's a buddy of mine.
He's down on his luck
so I gave him the job,
knowing he'll give it his best shot.
But...
But? You should talk!
Call him now and find out where he is.
(Brother Kui)
Boss!
Did you lose your gun?
Damn! He found out. What now?
You should talk. The locker was empty.
No gun?
Ask him...
No way. The Boss said he put
the gun in the locker.
How come?
There was nothing in the locker.
What did you put it into?
What box did you use? Was it stolen?
Did that guy want the Gundam box?
He pried open the locker after I left?
Here's my Boss...
That creep Wong Sai-lung?
What have you been doing?
I'm trying to figure out how to kill
without a gun.
Why bother? We got the gun back.
I'll personally hand it to you.
Where should we meet? Name the place.
I did my research. The cold storage
on the ground floor has less traffic.
Go down there now.
My Boss will meet you there and
hand you the gun.
Hey...what does he look like?
White hair dude wearing a uniform.
Easy to spot.
OK!
Wong Sai-lung will give me the gun.
I can shoot him on the spot.
Bloody hell, why the cold storage
of all places?
This is nuts!
OK, Silver Fox. I'm giving
the gun to you again.
Don't waste any more time.
Go kill Chin Tai-fu right away. Hurry...